Peace, mercy and blessings be upon you. How are you?
السلام عليكم يااهلا وسهلا  كيف حالكم انشاءالله
Good
طيبين
Today Jaipin your video is a strange time
اليوم جايبين لكم  فيديو مره غريب
Once a strange time
مره مره مره غريب
Imagine, we are back to Saudi Arabia
تخيلو انا رجعنا السعوديه
احنا دحين في بيتنا
I know Shi was crazy about you
داري كان شي مجنون بالنسبه لكم
Surprisingly a great time for most people
مفاجأه مره كبيره لاغلب الناس
سوف أجعلكم تشاهدون كل شئ، وأشرح لكم لماذا حضرنا إلي هنا وماذا فعلنا!
حتار ترا اهلنا ماكان يدرون عن المفاجأهذي
But God's section is enthusiastic
لاكن اقسم بالله مره متحمسين
The room is the most important and how you
And of course, as always, everything
Of course I am explaining everything
طبعا انا الي اشرح انا كل شي
The bandages of the time were churned out of the fridge
يواد من زمان  ماشربت مويه من البراده
Wow
وااااووو
God is Hamas
والله حماس
And we have saved the violin violin from our house
Of course, this is the first gift we made of course
طبعا هاذي اول هديه جتنا صوره طبعا
One of the followers Sualna Come on
هاذي من احد المتابعين سوالنا هيا
The important thing we enter
المهم خلنا نخش
Ready
جاهز
And we say in the name of God to enter
ونقول  بسم الله لنخش
My heart is very enthusiastic and my darling is very enthusiastic
وربي متحمس دقيقه وربي داري كلكم متحمسين نشوف من زمان ما شفتوها
I know from time to time, but before the passage I entered my poems
ادري من زمان ماشفناها بس قبل المقطع دخلت حطيت اشيائي
But Borikm it once again strong
لاكن بوريكم اياها بصوره مره قويه
لاكن بوريكم ياها بصوره مره قويه
But Borikm it once again strong
One two three times
واحد,ثنين ,ثلاثاااااااااااااا
Macha Allah and God from time to time
ماشاءالله ووالله من مان عنها
Peace, mercy and blessings be upon you. How are you?
Good
Today Jaipin your video is a strange time
Once a strange time
Imagine, we are back to Saudi Arabia
We are now in our house
I know Shi was crazy about you
Surprisingly a great time for most people
Our people were not aware of this surprise
But God's section is enthusiastic
The room is the most important and how you
And of course, as always, everything
Of course I am explaining everything
The bandages of the time were churned out of the fridge
Wow
God is Hamas
And we have saved the violin violin from our house